Inventory of the Papers of Monroe Leigh, 1941 - 2001
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Legal Papers
  - International Water Rights
    - Memorandum re: International Joint Commissions on Lake of the Woods Watershed, 28 March 1949 (Box-folder 42 - 3)
      Contains 1 document titled: "Recommendations of International Joint Commission on Diversion from Watershed in Its Final Report on the Lake of the Woods Reference"
    - St. Lawrence Seaway: Public Law 358, House Report 1215, Senate Report 441, 1953, 1954, 1957 (Box-folder 42 - 4)
      Contains markup, handwritten notations, circled areas regarding the relevant aspects to international water rights vis-à-vis the St. Lawrence Seaway between Canada and the US. Includes Public Law 358, 83d Congress, Chapter 201, 2d Session, S. 2150 (July 1957), "Report on the Committee on Public Works on S.2150: A Bill providing for creation of the St. Lawrence Seaway Development Corporation to Construct part of the St. Lawrence Seaway in United States Territory and for other purposes," House Report No. 1215, 83d Congress, 2d Session (February 19, 1954), Senate Report No. 441 (same name House Report No. 1215), 83d Congress, 1st Session (June 16, 1953)
    - Helmand/Hirmand River Dispute between Iran and Afghanistan - I, [1950] (Box-folder 42 - 5)
      Contains copies of treaties, memos, drafts, relevant background/precedent materials, notes, handwritten notations, edits, markup, revisions
    - Helmand/Hirmand River Dispute between Iran and Afghanistan - II, [1950] (Box-folder 42 - 6)
    - Helmand/Hirmand River Dispute between Iran and Afghanistan - Annex G, [1950] (Box-folder 42 - 7)
      Contains initials ML
  - Case Files
    - Shipping Valuation Case Summaries I - III, [1948] (Box-folder 42 - 8)
      Contains cases American Hawaiian Steamship Co. v. United States, Baltimore Steam Packet v. United States, Cors v. United States
    - Shipping Valuation Case Summaries IV - VII, [1948] (Box-folder 42 - 9)
      Contains cases Eastern Steamship Lines v. United States, Kendall v. United States, Lex Laboratories, Inc. v. United States
    - Shipping Valuation Case Summaries VIII - XIV, [1948] (Box-folder 42 - 10)
      Contains cases Natioanl Bulk Carriers v. United States, North American Shipping Company v. United States, Olive J. Olson & Company v. United States, Ozanic v. United States, Petition of Grace Lines, Smith-Douglass Company v. United States, Trailerships Inc. v. United States, Wilson Lines v. United States
    - Just Compensation - Legislative History, Dec 1948 - Jan 1949 (Box-folder 43 - 1)
      Contains an overview of legislation and cases related to Just Compensation
    - Danish Ships: Just Compensation Data on Five Danish Vessels Requisitioned 12 July 1941, [1948] (Box-folder 43 - 2)
      Contains summary of compromise settlement offer of just compensation for five danish vessels requisitioned July 12, 1941, including the Alssund, Brosund, Columbia, Lundby, Olympia
    - Danish Ships: Just Compensation Case Draft, 7 Dec 1949 (Box-folder 43 - 3)
      Contains draft "Report for H. Graham Morison, Assistant Attorney General, Claims Division, Department of Justice
    - Danish Ships: Athene, 28 Aug 1948 (Box-folder 43 - 4)
      Contains memorandum for Mr. Bressor, Message for Mr. Howard, Memorandum for Mr. Laylin
    - Danish Ships: Lundby, 11 Sept 1948 (Box-folder 43 - 5)
      Contains memorandum for Conference with Paul Umoff, Memorandum of Conference with J. G. Comyn, Memorandum of Conference with H. A. Stevenson, Memorandum of Conference with George Davies
    - Danish Ships: Depositions, 11 Sept 1948 (Box-folder 43 - 6)
      Contains Deposition of Hans Christian Brodersen and the Deposition of Hugo Lund for Dampskibsselskabet "Haffnia" Aktieselskab, et al vs. The United States in the United States Court of Claims
    - Christiani and Nielsen Visa Matter, 1943 - 1949 (Box-folder 43 - 7)
      Binder with 16 sections regarding "Christiani Visa Matter" that deals with citizenship and whether or not Henning Christiani was a collaborator with the Germans during World War II. Sections include: Memorandum for Mr. Laylin, 1. Christiani and Nielsen Memorandum, 2. letter to Henning Christiani, 3. Memo of a conversation between Mr. Steger and Mr. Hyde at the U.S. Consulate on 12th January 1948, 4. Telephone conversation of December 11, 1947 with Francis Cunningham of State Department, concerning visas, 5. Translation of Depostition made by former Prime Minister Erik Scavenius before the investigating committee of hte Engineering Society in the matter of the investigation of the conduct of its member, Dr. Rud. Christiani, during the late war, 6. "Danish Saboteurs Wreck Nazi Plants" text from New York Times article dated Sunday, February 21, 1943, 7. "Nazis Hinted Giving Up Norway and Denmark" text from New York World-Telegram article dated Thursday, February 3, 1944, 8. "Nazis Plan to Leave Norway, Denmark" text from The London Daily Sketch artcled dated Thursday, February 3, 1944, 9. Statement (from Christiani?), 10. Translation of Memorandum on the Work of Ardal, 11. Translation of Letter of Auugst 19, 1949, from Dr. Christiani to Mr. Henning O. Christiani, New York, in excerpt, 12. Translation of memorandum from Mr. C. L. David, barrister to the Supreme Court, to Mr. Steglich-Petersen, barrister to the Supreme Court, regarding Dr. Rud. Christiani vs. The Danish Engineering Society dated August 15, 1949, in excerpt, 13. Translation of letter of April 20, 1949, from the Ministry of Justice to Mr. Steglich-Petersen, attorney for Dr. Rud Christiani, informing Mr. Steglich-Petersen that the Ministry of Justice has written the Attorney General that they accept his recommendation that hte Ministry not take up again the matter of violation of hte ex post facto laws relating to association with the enemy during the occupation of which Dr. Christiani was absolved of February 7, 1947, -- in spite of additional relevant data extracted by the investigating committee of the Danish Engineering Society, 14. Translation Royal Danish Legation letter, 15. Translation of letter of June 13, 1949, from Dr. Rud. Christiani to Mr. Henning O. Christiani, care of Christiani & Nielsen Ltda, Bogota, Colombia, in excerpt, 16. Translation of letter between Henning O. Christiani and Christiani & Nielsen / Rud Christiani
    - Fritze Case: Alien Property Custodian, Apr. 1947 - Jan. 1948 (Box-folder 43 - 8)
      Contains facts of the case, memorandum, notes, supplemental memorandum, Brief of Claimant on Motion to Dismiss, H.R. 5200 (80th Congress, 2d Session), markup, looseleaf handwritten notes, edits [Case revolves around the question of "whether an individual who is an American citizen by American law and at the same time a German citizen by German law, may recover property seized by the Alien Property Custodian during WWII"]
    - Renegotiation Cases Memoranda, 30 Dec 1947 - 7 Apr 1948 (Box-folder 43 - 9)
      Contains handwritten looseleaf notes, drafts, edits, markup
    - Abstracts of Sales Contracts - Chronological, [1948] (Box-folder 43 - 10)
      Contains brief overviews of sales contracts involving shipping via water (ocean/sea), including Name, D.W.T., Age, Date of Sale, Seller, Buyer, Consideration, Price per D.W.T., Terms of Payment, Port of Delivery, and Conditions, from July 1940 to October 1945
    - Abstracts of Sales Contracts - Alphabetical, [1948] (Box-folder 43 - 11)
    - FCC - Use of Telephone recording devices, 1948 (Box-folder 43 - 12)
      Contains orders, memorandum, handwritten notations, looseleaf notes,
    - Union Underwear Company Memoranda, 31 Jan - 18 June 1948 (Box-folder 43 - 13)
    - Richard S. Cors v. the United States - Abstracts and Legislative History, [1948] (Box-folder 43 - 14)
      Involves rights of ships and the Federal Government, contains Abstracts of Cases for Cors Argument, memorandum, handwritten notations, looseleaf notes, edits, discussions on the authority of "the Maritime Commission to requisition ships of foreign registry lying idle in American ports," the "enhancement clause," Report: Inquiry into operations, policies, and affairs of United States shipping board and emergency fleet corporation by the House of Representatives, 69th Congress, 1st Sesstion (Report No. 2)
    - Richard S. Cors v. the United States - Court Documents [1948] (Box-folder 43 - 15)
      Contains printed proceedings of case, court documents (both for the Court of Claims phase and the US Supreme Court phase), includes markup, handwritten notations
    - Accumulation Clause re: Upson Will materials, 1950 (Box-folder 44 - 1)
      Contains overview of case, background information, materials on other related cases, handwritten notations, looseleaf notes,
    - Wills, 1950 (Box-folder 44 - 2)
      Includes copies of 5 wills for Adda M. Allen, Janet H. C. Meade, Jane Kelley Caskey, Howard T. Karsner, Frank R. Jelleff,
    - A. B. Chandler - Unfair Competition jurisdiction, 1950 (Box-folder 44 - 3)
      Contains memoranda, court documents, depositions, handwritten notes, looseleaf notes, edits, markup, drafts, discussion of "whether the Commissioner of Baseball may not be deemed a one-man voluntary association," national law of unfair competition, piracy complaint in connection with world series broadcast, copyright problems involved in televising the Cinema
    - American Airlines - Mexican Route Case, 1950 (Box-folder 44 - 4)
      Contains memoranda, index cards, handwritten notations, looseleaf notes, discusses questions re: "whether the President proceeding under his executive powers may cancel the certificates of publi convenience and necessity issued to certain domestic air carriers authorizing them to fly to Mexico City."
    - British Telecom: FedEx receipt and copy of letter to British Telecommunications PLC re: Stratos signature page for the Completion Balance Sheet, 29 June 2001 (Box-folder 44 - 5)
    - Miscellaneous Cases Memoranda (1), Mar. - Dec. 1947 (Box-folder 44 - 6)
      Contains drafts, edits, markup, looseleaf handwritten notes, newspaper clippings
    - Miscellaneous Cases Memoranda (2), Jan - Dec 1948 (Box-folder 44 - 7)
      Contains drafts, edits, looseleaf handwritten notes, handwritten notations
    - Miscellaneous Cases Memoranda (3), Jan - Nov 1849 (Box-folder 44 - 8)
      Contains drafts, edits, handwritten notations
    - Miscellaneous Cases Memoranda (4), Jan - June 1950 (Box-folder 44 - 9)
    - Miscellaneous Cases Memoranda (5), July - Dec 1950 (Box-folder 44 - 10)
    - Miscellaneous Cases Memoranda (6), Jan - Mar 1951 (Box-folder 44 - 11)
    - Miscellaneous Cases Index Cards, n.d. (Box-folder 44 - 12)
      Contains 27 index cards with summaries of relevant cases for precedent purposes under the headings of arbitration, Condemnation, Contract, Fiscal Year, Lease, Reimbursement,
- Personal Papers
  - Correspondence
    - Notes on Cases for London Economist Article, Mar - July 1948 (Box-folder 45 - 1)
      Contains notes by Monroe Leigh, Orem W. Ketchum, J. K. M., H. R. S., W. S. S., D. V. H., Jr., C. J. S., includes markup, adites, handwritten notes, looseleaf notes, index card
    - Drafts of London Economist Article, 17745 (Box-folder 45 - 2)
      Contains 31 July 1948 edition of The Economist with article submitted by Leigh, various drafts of said article
    - Ephemera, n.d., 1952, 1955 (Box-folder 45 - 3)
      Contains "Progress of Bankruptcy" framed cartoon (n.d.), University of London Presentation Ceremony for Recipients fo Higher Degrees and Reception by the Vice-Chancellor program (21 March 1952), "Law Notes" notebook that lists persons met/present at social functions and those who sent Monroe Leigh Christmas Cards, The University of Virginia and the Spirit of Honor by Robert K. Gooch, An address to teh entering students, 19 Sept 1955
    - Personal Correspondence, 1958 (Box-folder 45 - 4)
      Contains handwritten letters, envelopes, enclosures, invitations, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Gerald I. A. D. Draper, Dietrich Oehler, Howard E. Hensleigh, Old Ivy Inn, Robert Hubbard, Jr., Raymond F. Loving, Farmington Country Club, John R. Dykema, Hardy C. Dillard, Arthur J. Walters, Bumpus Book Store, Richard (Dick) R. Baxter, Donald P. Ray, Helen M. Hill, Roger Fisher, Lindsey Cowen, R. D. G. Ribble, Marjorie Merritt, Channing Harrison, E. Ham. Welbourn, John S. Voorhees, Michael H. Cardozo, Adam Yarmolinsky, Davidson Sommers, Walter H. Glass, Louis Henkin, Department of Motor Vehicles, Alan Burroughs, Klemens von Klemperer, William H. Smith, Robert W. Tucker, Charles T. Berry, Evans B. Brasfield, F. Aley Allan, Reverend Daniel E. Power, Comptroller of the Treasury, Office of the Assessor, District Collector of Internal Revenue, Henry Saunders, F. A. Cardman, Joseph Burchenal, London Life Association Ltd, Robert Haydock
    - Norman Frauenheim, 1958 - 1971 (Box-folder 45 - 5)
      Contains looseleaf notes, Conclusions in response document, French Republic in the Name of the French People document, handwritten notations and edits in french, Correspondents include: Jane Lang McGrew, Norman Frauenheim, F. A. Mann, Monroe Leigh, Trustee Department - General Accident, Fire and Life Assurance Corporation, Ltd.,
    - Personal Correspondence, 1959 (Box-folder 45 - 6)
      Contains note cards, newspaper clippings, handwritten letters, letter drafts, envelopes, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, U. S. Department of Commerce, Vincent Burke, John N. Irwin II, George W. Hickman, Nugroho, Joseph C. Robert, Robert H. Knight, David Bruce, Paul Kaplowitz, Wilmington Trust Company, Donald E. Claudy, Robert Dechert, Manhattan Traffic Court, Robert Fearey, Paul A. Wolkin, John R. Dykema, Heyward Isham, Totton P. Heffelfinger II, Union Trust Company, Her Majesty's Stationary Office, Belgian Consul General, Tom W. Leigh, Roy D. Russell, Benjamin Forman, Regal Shoe Shop, Nicholas deB. Katzenbach, R. E. Booker, G. Vernon Leopold, R. E. Bauer, Howard Hensleigh, John D. Epperly, Walter, Glass, Superintendent of Documents, John N. Bathrick, Leonard J. Ganse, John Haskell, Bumpus Book Store, George Hsu & Company, Blackwell's, Sheldon Z. Kaplan, Philip O'Neill, Jimmy, John McGlynn, Sherman Baldwin, Catharine Gallaher, Wilson E. Schmidt, Jere H. Dkyema, John D. Epperly, Henry W. Sawyer, III, Joseph M. Snee, Edwin G. Schuck, Luke Marbury, Carl, Z. Lewis Dalby, J. W. Lentz, Jack Osborne, Charles Davis, Folger, Nolan, Fleming - W. B. Hibbs & Co., Inc., Gerald I. A. D. Draper, Mansfield D. Sprague, William Gallaher, Arthur H. Phillips, Frank Shakelford, O. M. Scott, Robert G. Harper, David Bruce, Edwin McElwain, Lyttleton Fox, Myres S. McDougal, H. M. Stationary Office, Don V. Harris, Jr., Marshal, Stephen Hearst, Roland, John B. Henderson, Edward Lee Arapian, Dillard Crinkley, William W. Arbuckle, Thomas Armat, Jr., Mrs. Hugh Gallaher, Gianni (Johnny) Manca, Robert (Bob) Haydock, Ammi Cutter, H. Marshall Peter, Charlie Maechling, Father James F. Cunningham,
    - Personal Correspondence, January - June, 1960 (Box-folder 45 - 7)
      Contains signatures, handwritten comments, enclosures, looseleaf notes, pamphlets, brochures, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Daingerfield L. Ashton, Benjamin Forman, Marjorie Merritt, John D. Randall, Richard R. Baxter, Stephen Hearst, Jackson Martindell, Tracy S. Voorhees, The Ronald Press Company, M. W. Oettershagen, Little Falls Swimming Club, Thomas P. Peardon, Nugroho, Michael H. Cardozo, Gerald I. A. D. Draper, Howard E. Hensleigh, John F. Furman, Blackwell's Music Shop, F. Warrington Dawson, J. Vincent Burke, Jr., F. J. Dymond, Leonard C. Meeker, Irving Lipkowitz, J. W. Iliff, Wallace Dempsey, Lybrand, Ross Brothers & Montgomery, Walter Herzfeld, Ercole Graziadei, Mrs. McCannon, E. Earl Pugh, Robert W. Berry, Siesta Motel, Louis C. Krauthoff, Byron S. Adams, Simeon B. Dunlap Smith, Rene-Jean Wilhelm, Joseph Burchenal, T. A. Grillo, Tyler Thompson, Phillip I.Blumberg, I. Austin Heyman, Lyttleton Fox, Brockenbrough Lamb, The Old Ivy Inn, George W. Hickman, Jr., Jackson K. Judy, Jerome P. Facher, George R. Fetter, Robert M. Scott, Sam Clammer, L. L. Lemnitzer, Sidney Morton, Ernest A. Jaffray, E. Hambleton Welbourn, Jr., Hugh Gallaher, Theodore C. Achilles, Alan S. Boyd, Anna Barringer, Henry W. Sawyer, III, Harvard Law Review, William Leigh Taylor, Walter Glass, Edwin Martin, W. T. M. Beale, Jr., James Fulton, Joseph Barbash, Ben Bruce Blakeney, Leonard J. Saccio, Vester T. Hughes, Jr., Conrad Philos, G. Gale Roberson, Jr., Frank Boas, Chase Manhattan Bank, J & E Bumpus, Ltd., John Cheeseright, Charles Foster Moore,
    - Personal Correspondence, July - December, 1960 (Box-folder 45 - 8)
      Contains signatures, handwritten comments, underlines, Correpondents include: Monroe Leigh, Warrington Dawson, Walton Folk, Marjorie G. McCannon, Elliott B. Strauss, Lewis H. Van Dusen, John B. Rehm, John G. Burnett, K. H. Friedman, Charles Rhyne, Norman P. Seagrave, Herbert F. Goodrich, Leslie A. Boosey, E. J. O'Donnell, J. Vincent Burke, Jr., Benjamin Forman, John B. Henderson, Roger Ernst, Richard R. Baxter, William E. Perdew, Samuel L. Eggleston, Herman C. Marshall, Gerald Draper, Bill, Blackwell's Book Store, Tracy S. Voorhees, A. W. H. Nicholson, Lewis H. Van Dusen, Jr., Thomas P. Peardon, William McC. Martin, Jr., D. Webster, Mansfield Sprague, Lynn Ungoed-Thomas, Bankers Trust Company, Stephen Hearst, G. I. A. D. Draper, Comptroller of the Treasury, Joseph T. Trotter, A. E. Kraus, Madeleine Provinzano, Lyman L. Lemintzer, Max G. Coulson, Doubleday Book Shop, Union Trust Company, Rene-Jean Wilhelm, Howard E. Hensleigh, H & P Manufacturing Company, F. Trowbridge vom Bauer, Herbert J. Blitz, Lyttleton Fox, E. Hambleton Welbourn, Jr.
    - Gerald Draper Correspondence, 1960 - 1974 (Box-folder 46 - 1)
      Contains underlines, handwritten notations, signatures, Correspondents include: Julia and Gerald I. A. D. L. Al Forge, Draper, Monroe Leigh,
    - Personal Correspondence, 1961 (Box-folder 46 - 2)
      Contains handwritten letters, looseleaf pages, envelopes, enclosures, resumes, newspaper clippings, Correspondents include: Sidney Morton, SCM, Mr. Guiher, Mr. Morris, Charles Donahue, Donald J. Hardenbrook, William C. Bauknight, Julius Kaplan, Richard C. Bergen, Walter H. Glass, Charles H. Shuff, Robert A. Marmet, John N. Regan, Dumond Peck Hill, Market Tire Company, Macon M. Arthur, Gustave M. Hauser, Adam Yarmolinsky, Union Trust Company, Perkins McGuire, Aley Allan, Joel Barlow, Edward D. Re, Nicholas Katzenbach, John E. Hayes, Wallace G. Dempsey, Arthur H. Phillips, Stanley Surrey, John Dykema, Robert W. Lawson, Jr., Edward S. Smith, J. W. Weaver, Samuel Efron, Eastern Airlines, K. H. Friedman, Tracy S. Voorhees, Peter von Teufenstein, John Stuart Higgins Jr., Martin Domke, Alfred von Klemperer, Helen Claggett, John B. Huffaker, Dan Marquarder, H. F. Arps, William J. Schrenk, Jr., John Carey, Mansfield D. Sprague, Federal Trade Commission, Better Business Bureau, Washington Post, Department of Licenses & Inspection, William H. Watts, Stephen C. Reville, Jr., George C. Denney, Clovis E. Byers, Lawrence Hargie, Philip D. Saxon, Marjorie Merritt, Dick van Wagener, Philip D. Saxony, Richard (Dick) R. Baxter, John Stewart Higgins, Jr., Richard M. Buxbaum, Seymour J. Rubin, Hubert A. Schneider, Herbert Briggs, William Roy Vallance, Clovis Byers, John D. Epperly, Howard S. Levie, Charles R. Norberg, George Farah, Jacob L. Holtzmann, Irving Lipkowitz, Gerald I. A. D. Draper, Rev. Oscar deWolf Randolph, Phillip I. Blumberg, Jefferson B. Fordham, Robert Dechert, R. Granville Curry, Alan G. Kirk II, Bernard G. Heinzen, L. Niederlehner, Frank M. Wozencraft, Michael Cardozo, E. Fontaine Broun, C. Severin Buschmann, Jr., James C. Sargent, Alan S. Boyd, Daggett (Bud) Howard, Her Majesty's Stationary Office, Benjamin Forman, Charles L. Decker, Virginia Law Review Association, Collins Denny, III, Conrad Philos, Old Ivy Inn, Max Lehrer, L. Addison Lanier, Hudon's, J. Jacobs Shannen, Fisher Radio Warehouse, Georg Hukman, Z. Lewis Dalby, Glenn R. Winters, Alfred H. Von Klemperer, Brentano's, Blackwell's, John G. Burnett, Frank L. Dennis, A. Rushton, George W. Hickman, Lewis H. Van Dusen, George M. Coburn, Paul Nitze,
    - Personal Correspondence, 1962 (Box-folder 46 - 3)
      Contains handwritten letters, envelopes, enclosures, invitations, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, David I. Johnston, Rodrigo Llorente, James R. Patton, Jr., Virginia Law Review Association, Henry Dolz, Allen Communications, Lindsey Cowen, Walter Sterling Surrey, John B. Henderson, J. de Tender, Hugh Calkins, Richard (Dick) R. Baxter, Samuel B. Sterrett, James R. Patton, Tatlana Guldberg, Robert H. Knight, E. Hambleton (Ham) Welbourn, Jr., Norman Seagrave, Epsilon of Chi Phi, Secretary to General Gruenther, K. H. Friedman, Ralph Immell, Edwin Martin, Alfred M. Gruenther, Howard S. Levie, Sweet & Maxwell Ltd., A. Moreni, Robert H. Haden, Abram Chayes, Stevens and Sons, Vada Horsch, Wagons-Lits, American Airlines, Richard Swift, Messrs. Guiher and Morris, Walter H. Glass, Royal Little, Russell Baird Adams, F. Aley Allan, Douglass Cater, G. O. J. van Tets, Hubert A. Schneider, Mr. William Merriam, Henry F. Butler, Ralph Wesley Golby, Secretary - Metropolitan Club, Maxwell M. Caskie, Jr., Jerome P. Facher, Roger Fisher, Noyes Thompson (Tom) Powers, Stanley V. Malcuit, Guerin Todd, Wallace G. Dempsey, Gertrude C. Whitaker, Lewis Matacia, James Sargent, C. Richard Locke, Juraj L. J. Slavik, John Andrews King, Jr., Bourke B. Hickenloper, Rufus King, Ina Walker, Nugroho, Sidney Morton, Jack H. Pender, Frank Shackelford, John B. Henderson, Daggett (Bud) H. Howard, Ray Brittinham, The Treasurer - Metropolitan Club, Stephen C. Hopkins, Sr., Stephen Reville, George M. Pavia, Leon Lipson, John P. Furman, James P. Sullivan, Cecil J. Olmstead, Herman Finkelstein, John King, Jr., Louis C. Krauthoff, Nicholas deB. Katzenbach, John DeHardit, Chesapeake & Potomac Telephons, Harvard Business Review, Judson T. Vaughan, Jr., Phillip D. Jackson, Hart Perry, Warren Lee Pierson, Palmer S. Rutherford, Jr., John Emerson, Chris Nolde, Irving Lipkowitz, William Barron, Harry Catlin, Mrs. Hugh Gallaher, Ed Stern, Ken Hadow, Robert H. Haden, Henry Dolz
    - Personal Correspondence, 1963 (Box-folder 46 - 4)
      Contains invitations, notecards, envelopes,newspaper clippings, Correspendents include: Monroe Leigh, Riggs National Bank, Robert Haydock, First National City Bank, Michael H. Cardozo, George W. Ray, Jr., District Director of Internal Revenue, Sidney E. King, Vester T. Hughes, Jr., Herman Marshall, Raymond O. Mulvany, John Richardson, John Langstaff, Don V. Harris, Jr., Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York, Rita E. Hauser, Philip I. Blumberg, Clive L. DuVal, II, Walter H. Glass, Elbert Cox, Thomas E. Gilmer, Robert Dechert, Stephen Reville, Jr., James E. Edmunds, The Strad Office, Chase Manhattan Bank, Allan E. Walker, Jr., W. Taylor Reveley, Jr., William Thomas, Walter A. Willson, III, Robert Anthoine, Howard Marshall Holtzmann, R. M. Eager, Cecil J. Olmstead, Janet H. C. Mead, Ed Fish, Jesse Guy Benson, Philip S. Bowie, Vincent J. Hearing, Frank Shackelford, Benjamin Montmorency Tench, Jr., Carol Sue Richard, John W. Leatherman, Fannie J. Klein, Richard Baxter, Aunt Bee, Robert A. Falise, Henry B. Smythe, John H. Fanning, Phillip Blumberg, William Bryan, Mrs. William Denson, Controller of the Treasury, Messrs F. Trobridge vom Baur, Spencer M. Beresford & George M. Coburn, Howard Hensleigh, Charles L. Decker, Hugh Calkins, Eugene B. Thomas, Romer McPhee, David Johnston, Richard Young, Alfred M. Gruenther
    - Gen Kajitani Correspondence, 1963 - 1973 (Box-folder 46 - 5)